<response>

  <day date="January 6, 2025">
    # Weekly Marketing Meeting
    Date: January 6, 2025
    Time: 10:00 AM - 10:45 AM

    ## Attendees
    Olivia Brooks, Daniel Reed, Ava Collins, Liam Harris, Sophia Turner

    ## Agenda
    - Brand Refresh Project Updates
    - Social Media & Influencer Strategy Checkpoint
    - Upcoming Webinar Plans

    ---
    ## Discussions
    1. **Brand Refresh Rollout**  
       - Daniel shared updated mockups of the new logo and color scheme.  
       - Team provided feedback on color accessibility and usage guidelines.

    2. **Social Media & Influencer Outreach**  
       - Ava proposed a TikTok influencer campaign targeting Gen Z.  
       - Olivia suggested focusing on LinkedIn for B2B opportunities.

    3. **Quarterly Webinar**  
       - Sophia outlined a timeline for securing speakers and topics.  
       - Liam proposed a thought-leadership angle focusing on industry trends.

    ---
    ## Action Items
    - Daniel: Finalize brand guidelines draft [Due: Next Meeting]
    - Ava: Identify 3 potential TikTok influencers [Due: January 13]
    - Sophia: Prepare a short list of webinar speakers [Due: January 13]
  </day>

  <day date="January 13, 2025">
    # Weekly Marketing Meeting
    Date: January 13, 2025
    Time: 10:03 AM - 10:50 AM

    ## Attendees
    Olivia Brooks, Daniel Reed, Ava Collins, Liam Harris, Sophia Turner

    ## Agenda
    - Brand Guidelines Draft Review
    - Influencer Selection for TikTok Campaign
    - Webinar Speaker Updates

    ---
    ## Discussions
    1. **Brand Guidelines Progress**  
       - Daniel presented finalized color palette and brand voice guidelines.  
       - Olivia recommended cross-checking brand voice with legal requirements.

    2. **Influencer Outreach**  
       - Ava shortlisted three TikTok influencers; consensus to engage them on a pilot basis.  
       - Sophia suggested scheduling short intro calls with each influencer.

    3. **Webinar Speaker Updates**  
       - Sophia has reached out to 2 potential speakers; waiting on confirmation.  
       - Liam to collaborate with speakers on content topics.

    ---
    ## Action Items
    - Daniel: Incorporate legal team feedback into brand guidelines [Due: January 20]
    - Ava & Sophia: Begin initial contact with chosen influencers [Due: January 16]
    - Liam: Draft a webinar content outline [Due: January 20]
  </day>

  <day date="January 20, 2025">
    # Weekly Marketing Meeting
    Date: January 20, 2025
    Time: 10:05 AM - 10:45 AM

    ## Attendees
    Olivia Brooks, Daniel Reed, Ava Collins, Liam Harris

    ## Agenda
    - Finalizing Brand Refresh
    - Influencer Contract Details
    - Webinar Content Outline

    ---
    ## Discussions
    1. **Brand Refresh Completion**  
       - Daniel confirmed legal compliance; brand guidelines are ready for company-wide rollout.  
       - Olivia proposed internal training sessions to ensure brand consistency.

    2. **Influencer Contract Negotiations**  
       - Ava shared cost estimates and contract terms for the pilot campaign.  
       - Team discussed budget constraints and ROI expectations.

    3. **Webinar Content Outline**  
       - Liam presented the draft outline focusing on “Emerging Market Trends.”  
       - Olivia highlighted the need to tie the content back to lead generation goals.

    ---
    ## Action Items
    - Olivia: Schedule brand training sessions company-wide [Due: January 27]
    - Ava: Finalize influencer contract negotiations [Due: January 24]
    - Liam: Incorporate lead-gen angle into webinar outline [Due: January 27]
  </day>

  <day date="January 27, 2025">
    # Weekly Marketing Meeting
    Date: January 27, 2025
    Time: 10:00 AM - 10:55 AM

    ## Attendees
    Olivia Brooks, Daniel Reed, Ava Collins, Liam Harris, Sophia Turner

    ## Agenda
    - Brand Training Session Feedback
    - Pilot TikTok Campaign Launch
    - Webinar Logistics

    ---
    ## Discussions
    1. **Brand Training Sessions**  
       - Olivia reported positive feedback from internal teams.  
       - Daniel recommended collecting user stories to highlight brand usage.

    2. **Pilot TikTok Campaign**  
       - Ava confirmed influencer contracts are signed; campaign starts next week.  
       - The team discussed potential contingency plans if initial engagement is low.

    3. **Webinar Logistics**  
       - Sophia shared target date for the webinar (February 15).  
       - Liam to finalize speaker presentations and gather promotional materials.

    ---
    ## Action Items
    - Daniel: Compile brand usage stories for marketing materials [Due: February 3]
    - Ava: Coordinate next steps with influencers for soft launch [Due: January 31]
    - Sophia & Liam: Finalize webinar schedule and speaker slides [Due: February 3]
  </day>

  <day date="February 3, 2025">
    # Weekly Marketing Meeting
    Date: February 3, 2025
    Time: 10:00 AM - 10:40 AM

    ## Attendees
    Olivia Brooks, Daniel Reed, Ava Collins, Liam Harris

    ## Agenda
    - Initial TikTok Campaign Results
    - Brand Refresh Follow-Up
    - Webinar Promotion Plan

    ---
    ## Discussions
    1. **TikTok Campaign Performance**  
       - Ava shared early metrics: moderate engagement, with potential to improve content strategy.  
       - The team discussed adjusting creative briefs for the influencers.

    2. **Brand Refresh Follow-Up**  
       - Daniel collected brand usage stories; early feedback is positive.  
       - Olivia emphasized the importance of consistent brand adoption in all external-facing materials.

    3. **Webinar Promotion**  
       - Liam drafted social posts, email announcements, and blog teasers.  
       - Olivia wants a short promotional video to add visual appeal.

    ---
    ## Action Items
    - Ava: Update influencer guidelines with feedback from pilot results [Due: February 7]
    - Liam: Coordinate creation of a 30-second webinar promo video [Due: February 10]
    - Olivia: Approve final promotional assets before circulation [Due: February 7]
  </day>

  <day date="February 10, 2025">
    # Weekly Marketing Meeting
    Date: February 10, 2025
    Time: 10:06 AM - 10:50 AM

    ## Attendees
    Olivia Brooks, Daniel Reed, Ava Collins, Liam Harris, Sophia Turner

    ## Agenda
    - TikTok Content Adjustments
    - Webinar Final Prep
    - Content Marketing Strategy Review

    ---
    ## Discussions
    1. **Revised TikTok Campaign**  
       - Ava presented new content guidelines focusing on quick, punchy videos.  
       - Daniel suggested aligning visuals more closely with refreshed brand elements.

    2. **Webinar Final Prep**  
       - Sophia confirmed speaker slides are ready; final run-through scheduled for Friday.  
       - Liam confirmed the 30-second promo video is nearly complete.

    3. **Content Marketing Strategy**  
       - Team discussed SEO updates and new keywords to target.  
       - Daniel wants a consistent brand voice across blog posts and webinar materials.

    ---
    ## Action Items
    - Ava & Daniel: Sync brand visuals with TikTok content [Due: February 13]
    - Sophia: Conduct webinar rehearsal with speakers [Due: February 14]
    - Liam: Publish final promo video [Due: February 12]
  </day>

  <day date="February 17, 2025">
    # Weekly Marketing Meeting
    Date: February 17, 2025
    Time: 10:00 AM - 10:35 AM

    ## Attendees
    Olivia Brooks, Daniel Reed, Ava Collins, Sophia Turner

    ## Agenda
    - Webinar Debrief
    - Social/Influencer Performance
    - Upcoming Content Calendar

    ---
    ## Discussions
    1. **Webinar Debrief**  
       - Sophia reported 200 attendees; engagement was high in the Q&A session.  
       - Olivia wants to use recorded content for additional lead generation efforts.

    2. **Social/Influencer Performance**  
       - Ava noted improved TikTok campaign metrics, especially with new creative approach.  
       - Daniel proposed featuring influencer clips on the official company blog.

    3. **Content Calendar Plans**  
       - The team discussed upcoming blog themes around brand-building and post-webinar follow-up articles.  
       - Olivia recommended focusing on personalization in future marketing pushes.

    ---
    ## Action Items
    - Sophia: Edit and upload webinar recording to website [Due: February 20]
    - Ava: Gather final performance report for TikTok pilot [Due: February 24]
    - Daniel: Coordinate with Liam to feature influencer clips on blog [Due: February 24]
  </day>

  <day date="February 24, 2025">
    # Weekly Marketing Meeting
    Date: February 24, 2025
    Time: 10:02 AM - 10:45 AM

    ## Attendees
    Olivia Brooks, Daniel Reed, Ava Collins, Liam Harris, Sophia Turner

    ## Agenda
    - Webinar Lead Follow-Up
    - TikTok Pilot Report
    - Future Events & Conferences

    ---
    ## Discussions
    1. **Lead Follow-Up**  
       - Olivia reviewed new leads generated from the webinar; sales teams are actively reaching out.  
       - Liam suggested a personalized drip email sequence for these leads.

    2. **TikTok Pilot Report**  
       - Ava presented key engagement metrics: brand mentions increased by 15%, unique link clicks by 8%.  
       - Daniel praised the influencer collaboration, citing brand consistency improvements.

    3. **Future Events & Conferences**  
       - Sophia identified 2 major conferences in Q2 that the team may attend.  
       - Team debated whether to host a booth or focus on sponsoring specific sessions.

    ---
    ## Action Items
    - Liam: Draft a drip email workflow for new webinar leads [Due: February 28]
    - Ava: Propose next phase for influencer campaign [Due: March 3]
    - Sophia: Research sponsorship costs for Q2 conferences [Due: March 3]
  </day>

  <day date="March 3, 2025">
    # Weekly Marketing Meeting
    Date: March 3, 2025
    Time: 10:00 AM - 10:40 AM

    ## Attendees
    Olivia Brooks, Daniel Reed, Ava Collins, Liam Harris

    ## Agenda
    - Drip Email Workflow Review
    - Influencer Phase 2 Proposal
    - Q2 Conference Sponsorship Options

    ---
    ## Discussions
    1. **Drip Email Workflow**  
       - Liam presented a 4-email sequence targeting different lead segments.  
       - Olivia stressed the importance of clear CTAs in each email.

    2. **Influencer Campaign Phase 2**  
       - Ava suggested scaling the campaign to include short behind-the-scenes videos.  
       - Daniel recommended continuing with existing influencers before bringing in new ones.

    3. **Q2 Conference Sponsorship**  
       - Sophia shared initial costs and potential ROI.  
       - Team leaned toward partial sponsorship with a smaller booth presence.

    ---
    ## Action Items
    - Liam: Incorporate CTA improvements into drip campaign [Due: March 6]
    - Ava & Daniel: Refine Phase 2 influencer content plan [Due: March 7]
    - Sophia: Finalize partial sponsorship details [Due: March 7]
  </day>

  <day date="March 10, 2025">
    # Weekly Marketing Meeting
    Date: March 10, 2025
    Time: 10:05 AM - 10:50 AM

    ## Attendees
    Olivia Brooks, Daniel Reed, Ava Collins, Liam Harris, Sophia Turner

    ## Agenda
    - Drip Email Campaign Launch
    - Influencer Content Plan Check-in
    - Sponsorship Finalization

    ---
    ## Discussions
    1. **Email Campaign Launch**  
       - Liam confirmed final CTAs and branding tweaks are complete.  
       - Olivia announced the campaign goes live tomorrow.

    2. **Influencer Content Plan**  
       - Ava presented updated behind-the-scenes concepts; Daniel gave design feedback.  
       - Sophia suggested capturing user testimonials during filming if feasible.

    3. **Sponsorship Finalization**  
       - Sophia confirmed partial sponsorship details for the upcoming Q2 conference.  
       - Olivia requested a cost breakdown and timeline for marketing materials.

    ---
    ## Action Items
    - Liam: Monitor initial email campaign metrics for next week’s report [Due: March 17]
    - Ava: Coordinate filming schedule with influencers [Due: March 14]
    - Sophia: Provide final sponsor plan docs to leadership [Due: March 14]
  </day>

  <day date="March 17, 2025">
    # Weekly Marketing Meeting
    Date: March 17, 2025
    Time: 10:00 AM - 10:40 AM

    ## Attendees
    Olivia Brooks, Daniel Reed, Ava Collins, Liam Harris

    ## Agenda
    - Email Campaign Early Metrics
    - Influencer Video Progress
    - Q2 Conference Prep

    ---
    ## Discussions
    1. **Email Campaign Metrics**  
       - Liam presented early data: open rates at 28%, CTR at 5%.  
       - Olivia is pleased with initial traction, but suggests testing different subject lines.

    2. **Influencer Video Updates**  
       - Ava said filming went smoothly, waiting on final edits.  
       - Daniel will review to ensure brand style consistency.

    3. **Q2 Conference Preparations**  
       - Team discussed booth design concepts and travel arrangements.  
       - Olivia set a goal of generating 50+ high-quality leads from the event.

    ---
    ## Action Items
    - Liam: Prepare A/B test for subject lines in next email batch [Due: March 24]
    - Ava & Daniel: Review final influencer video for brand compliance [Due: March 20]
    - Sophia: Coordinate booth design with events vendor [Due: March 21]
  </day>

  <day date="March 24, 2025">
    # Weekly Marketing Meeting
    Date: March 24, 2025
    Time: 10:00 AM - 10:45 AM

    ## Attendees
    Olivia Brooks, Daniel Reed, Ava Collins, Liam Harris, Sophia Turner

    ## Agenda
    - Email Campaign A/B Test Results
    - Influencer Video Release
    - Conference Logistics & Final Plans

    ---
    ## Discussions
    1. **A/B Test Results**  
       - Liam reported improved open rate (32%) and CTR (6.5%) with new subject lines.  
       - Olivia congratulated the team, noting a significant revenue potential if leads convert.

    2. **Influencer Video Launch**  
       - Ava posted final behind-the-scenes video series; initial views are promising.  
       - Daniel praised the alignment with the updated brand voice.

    3. **Conference Logistics**  
       - Sophia reviewed final booth design and travel schedule.  
       - Olivia reminded everyone to gather as much feedback and contact info as possible during the event.

    ---
    ## Action Items
    - Liam: Compile drip campaign conversion stats post-conference [Due: April 1]
    - Ava: Track influencer video metrics for monthly report [Due: April 1]
    - Sophia & Daniel: Ensure all booth materials align with brand guidelines [Due: March 28]
  </day>

</response>